<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Hugo-profile</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Hugo-profile</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 23:29:21 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/markdown-syntax/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Emoji Support</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/emoji-support/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/emoji-support/</guid><description>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.
The emojify function can be called directly in templates or Inline Shortcodes.
To enable emoji globally, set enableEmoji to true in your site’s configuration and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.
The Emoji cheat sheet is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.
N.B. The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform.</description></item><item><title>Placeholder Text</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/placeholder-text/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:41:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/placeholder-text/</guid><description>Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.
Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc caluere tempus inhospita parcite confusaque translucet patri vestro qui optatis lumine cognoscere flos nubis! Fronde ipsamque patulos Dryopen deorum.
Exierant elisi ambit vivere dedere Duce pollice Eris modo Spargitque ferrea quos palude Rursus nulli murmur; hastile inridet ut ab gravi sententia!</description></item><item><title>Rich Content</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/rich-content/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/rich-content/</guid><description>Hugo ships with several Built-in Shortcodes for rich content, along with a Privacy Config and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.
Gist Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; gist spf13 7896402 &amp;quot;img.html&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
Twitter Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; tweet 877500564405444608 &amp;gt;}}
Hugo 0.24 Released: Big archetype update + @Netlify _redirects etc. file supporthttps://t.co/X94FmYDEZJ #gohugo #golang @spf13 @bepsays
&amp;mdash; GoHugo.io (@GoHugoIO) June 21, 2017 Vimeo Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; vimeo 146022717 &amp;gt;}}</description></item></channel></rss>